Intercollegiate Athletics - Track, Women's Athletics Department, etc., Films and Video Tapes 1929-1977
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Intercollegiate Athletics - Track, Women's Athletics Department, etc., Films and Video Tapes
1929-1977
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections Pullman, WA 99164-5610 USA (509) 335-6691 http://www.wsulibs.wsu.edu/masc/ mascref@wsu.edu
Archives 213
approximate 60 items 1 linear feet 1 containers
Assorted WSU track and Women's Athletic Department films.
Organizational History:
Intercollegiate athletics at Washington State University are organized as a series of programs, each concerned with a specific type of sport, game or event. Certain sports (football and basketball) are organized around large staffs and organizations and are treated as distinct agencies within the University archives. Other sports are here combined as if one agency.
The arrangement of these films and videotapes is by sport, event or game, and chronologically thereunder.
The Collection is open for research use.
The films and tapes comprising this group of records came into the possession of the Washington State University Libraries at different times. Many items were included in Accession UA91-14, Basketball films. Many other were separated from Archives 28, office records from the Athletic Director. A few items are unrecorded accessions of individual films that were left at the Libraries at some time prior to 1991.
Washington State University. Sports.
College sports--Washington (State)--Archives
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities; Sports and Recreation; Moving Images
- Track and field events
  - Oregon Duel Meet, 1929; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Labeled, Bertoa?, 1962; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Labeled, G 3201, 1964; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Stanford, 1964; 2 reels (Box 1)
  - Oregon, 1964; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Oregon State, 1964; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Washington, 1964; 3 reels (Box 1)
  - Idaho, 1964; 2 reels (Box 1)
  - NCAA, 1964; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Practice, 1964; 2 reels (Box 1)
  - Oregon, 4/30/1966; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Regionals, 5/14/1966; 3 reels (Box 1)
  - PAC-8, at Eugene, Oregon, 5/19-20/1967; 3 reels (Box 1)
  - Javelin - Larry Hoover, 1970; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - High Jump \& Hurdles - Walters, 1970; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Triple Jump - Rorem, Olson, 1970; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Banana Belt at Cheney, 3/21/1970; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - WSU Invitational, 3/28/1970; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Oregon State, 4/4/1970; 4 reels (Box 1)
  - California, 4/18/1970; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Two mile relay, 1970; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Long Jump, 440 relay, 1970; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Mile, PU, High hurdles, etc., 1970; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Hi1, 1970 (Box 1)
  - NCAA, Provo, Utah -- BYU, 1975?; 2 reels (Box 1)
  - California, Triple, 880, I.H., UNKNOWN; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Hurdles, runs, UNKNOWN; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Javelin, UNKNOWN; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Shot / Sprints, UNKNOWN; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Mr. J. W. Mooberry, UNKNOWN; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Foss Miller, Hunnings, UNKNOWN; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Indoor, B/W, UNKNOWN; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Shotput, running Javelin, UNKNOWN; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Hurdles - Olson, UNKNOWN; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - 400 Meter Hurdles - Spike, UNKNOWN; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Unlabled films, UNKNOWN; 4 reels (Box 1)
  - Unlabled Super 8 films, UNKNOWN; 2 reels (Box 1)
  - Oregon (VHS), UNKNOWN; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Olympic Pole Vault, Super 8, 1968; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - WSU Cage Camp Promo (VHS), UNKNOWN; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Dial Classic, Championship Game, WSU - Gonzaga, (1/2" video), 1986; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - "Old Wazzu" promo. (1/2" video), UNKNOWN; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Debbie Rolph, Champion Baton Twirler, 16mm, B/W, ca. 1977; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Keith Jackson, for KWSU (1/2" video), 8/8/1986; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Boxing (Wisconsin '39, Stanford '36, Sacremento meet, '38; Intramural), 1936-1939; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Swimming, UNKNOWN; 1 reels (Box 1)
  - Track meet at Salt Lake City, Ut., 1947; 1 reels (Box 1)